For this application, I created two separate projects. One is a landing page with pure Javascript, and another is a React application. 

To have a single domain in Firebase, I had to have one root folder with the content of the landing page's files and a folder for the React app. I used Tailwind as a UI kit for my project because it is one of the latest UI kits that enhances the development phase. Also, I tried to write a custom hook because it increases reusability and flexibility. 

I found some vectors from Freepik and used them to create a condition of weather in Figma. 

Also, I designed the UI to make it engaging for viewers. 



Thank you for your consideration. 